gowealthy.com 2011-05-28

# Privacy Policy : Gowealthy.com

[

](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.gowealthy.com&sealid=101) | **GOWEALTHY.COM - PRIVACY STATEMENT  
       (Effective Date: 18 August 2008)  
**  
---|---  
  
**Gowealthy is committed to respecting and protecting your personal privacy. Our Privacy Policy is succinctly explained below. You can get additional details by clicking on the highlighted links. Also, please note that we strictly follow the COPPA guidance[click to know more](http://www.gowealthy.com/gowealthy/wcms/en/home/privacy-policy/index.html#egt) **

The site service provider, W3 informatics FZC on behalf of their client, gowealthy.com is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to enable individuals and organizations to establish trusting relationships based on respect for personal identity and information by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the site <http://www.gowealthy.com/>. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to our users' privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

1\. [What information Gowealthy collects from our site and how we use it?](http://www.gowealthy.com/gowealthy/wcms/en/home/privacy-policy/index.html#fst)  
2\. [What information third party may collect through the Web site.](http://www.gowealthy.com/gowealthy/wcms/en/home/privacy-policy/index.html#sec)  
3\. [With whom this information may be shared.](http://www.gowealthy.com/gowealthy/wcms/en/home/privacy-policy/index.html#trd)  
4\. [How gowealthy communicates through its members.](http://www.gowealthy.com/gowealthy/wcms/en/home/privacy-policy/index.html#frt)  
5\. [The users choices regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.](http://www.gowealthy.com/gowealthy/wcms/en/home/privacy-policy/index.html#fft)  
6\. [The security measures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Gowealthy control.](http://www.gowealthy.com/gowealthy/wcms/en/home/privacy-policy/index.html#sxt)  
7\. [How will the users be notified if Gowealthy change this privacy policy?](http://www.gowealthy.com/gowealthy/wcms/en/home/privacy-policy/index.html#svt)  
8\. [How user can correct any inaccuracies in the information.](http://www.gowealthy.com/gowealthy/wcms/en/home/privacy-policy/index.html#egt)  
9\. [Compliance with Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)](http://www.gowealthy.com/gowealthy/wcms/en/home/privacy-policy/index.html#nnt)  
10\. [Public Forum Disclaimer](http://www.gowealthy.com/gowealthy/wcms/en/home/privacy-policy/index.html#pfd)

* * *

**Your Questions or Suggestions Regarding This Privacy Policy :**

If users have any questions, concern or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us 

**Via Email**

For membership & general enquiries: [info@gowealthy.com](mailto:info@gowealthy.com)

Content related enquiries: [editor@gowealthy.com](mailto:editor@gowealthy.com)

Technical enquiries: [support@gowealthy.com](mailto:support@gowealthy.com)

Billing enquiries: [info@gowealthy.com](mailto:info@gowealthy.com)

Associates: [info@gowealthy.com](mailto:info@gowealthy.com)

Real estate enquiries: [info@gowealthy.com](mailto:info@gowealthy.com)

Project Status enquiries (UAE):  [status@gowealthy.com](mailto:status@gowealthy.com)

**Via Fax**

You can also fax the queries and the suggestions at 

UAE number  +971-6 5573751 

**Via E - Fax**

U.S.A - (718) 732-2985 

**Voice Mail**

E VOICE NUMBER (USA) 1-815-361-1887 

_Address for correspondence_

Website Managed and hosted by 

W3 informatics FZC  
A3-065, SAIF Zone,  
P.O. Box : 8945  
Sharjah, UAE. 

_Authorized Brand user in UAE_

First gowealthy Real Estate Brokers  
Emaar Business Park  
Suite 409, Bldg. 4  
Sheikh Zayed Road  
P.O.Box: 24620  
Dubai, UAE  
Tel:     +971 4 422 4777  
Fax:    +971 4 4224137  
E-mail: [info@gowealthy.com](mailto:info@gowealthy.com)

If you do not receive a satisfactory response, then please contact TRUSTe, an independent privacy organization that will contact us on your behalf. 

If they do not receive acknowledgment of their inquiry or their inquiry is not satisfactorily addressed, they should then contact TRUSTe through the [TRUSTe Watchdog Dispute Resolution Process (http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php)](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php). TRUSTe will serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve users concerns. 

* * *

**What Does the Gowealthy Privacy Policy Cover?**  
This privacy policy applies to web pages ending in Gowealthy.com that contain a link to this privacy policy at the bottom of the web page. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the site. By displaying the TRUSTe trust mark, www.gowealthy.com has agreed to notify users of: 

* * *

**1\. Information Collections and Use**  
The site service provider, W3 informatics FZC on behalf of their client, gowealthy.com is the sole owner of the information collected on Gowealthy.com. 

  * The user can visit our site and use most of our services without having to tell us who you are or reveal any personally identifiable information to Gowealthy. There are, however, a few instances where we do collect personally identifiable information in order to fulfill the users request.
  * When the user registers for premium service or register to use the forums section, Gowealthy ask for the information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. The information is collected to provide premium services to the members. The unique identifiers (username, password) are used to provide the personalized web services and tracking the user session. The other information is purely for internal statistic purpose. Once you register with Gowealthy and sign in to our services, the users are not anonymous to us.
  * Gowealthy uses all the information collected (anonymous and disclosed) to customize the users experience on gowealthy site and to improve our services in general. 
  * Gowealthy collect third party PII such as name and email to forward property listings and email articles and note that the information is not used for any other purposes but to send the one time email.
  * Links: This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, at Gowealthy, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Gowealthy uses cookies to manage the user state. Gowealthy does not use any persistent cookies. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We use only session ID cookies for the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. 

Gowealthy provides users third party cookies only for Ranking.com. Ranking.com performs statistical market research on website hits. By recording these surfers' website visits, Ranking.com calculates the ranking for the top 900,000 most visited websites and provides these results to surfers absolutely free. 

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. Whenever the user visits Gowealthy, our web browser automatically receives and record anonymous information. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Third Party Advertising**  
Gowealthy uses third-party ad servers to serve the advertisements that you see on the pages of our site. If you would like to know more about the information gathering practices of our third-party ad servers, please [click here](http://www.linkshare.com/home/privacy.shtml) for linkshare.com and [here](http://www.cj.com/privacy.html) for cj.com 

* * *

**2\. What information third party may collect through the Web site?**

  * In the few instances where Gowealthy collects personally identifiable information, Gowealthy will not share it with other companies or individuals unless: 
    1. We have your permission to share the information 
    2. We need to share your information with certain third parties with which we have a business relationship in order to provide a product or service you have requested. Unless we tell you otherwise, these third parties do not have the right to use your personal information we share with them beyond what is necessary to deliver your requested product or service; or 
    3. Legal Disclaimer - Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. 
  * Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable) we do not share aggregated demographic information with our advertisers. 
  * Supplementation of Information: In order for this Web site to properly fulfill its obligation to users it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources. 
    * Credit Card Payment for example during registration processes the user is required to make online payment. The credit card details are sent to third party server payment gateway ([2CheckOut](http://www.2checkout.com/) and [PayPal](https://www.paypal.com/) ) for acceptance through SSL encryption. Gowealthy does not store any kind information about credit card.
    * Currency Converter: Click here to view the privacy policy at [onada.com](http://www.oanda.com/site/legal/privacy.shtml). 
  * Third Party Advertisers -We have third party advertisers for ads, but no information what-so-ever is shared or allowed to access our user profile information.
  * Business Transitions - In the event another company goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquiring Gowealthy, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via email and prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If as a result of the business transition, the users' personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section. Furthermore, Gowealthy will not sell or disclose your personally identifiable information as customer lists to anyone for their promotional purposes. 

* * *

**3.With whom this information may be shared.**  
Gowealthy does not share the users information with the third party. The information collected is used purely to service the customers and for statistic purpose. Gowealthy does not use persistent cookies and cookies with identifiable details. How ever user can disable the cookie. The user listed for premium service can / withdraw his membership and ask for the permanent deletion of his details. The user can mail at [member@gowealthy.com](mailto:member@gowealthy.com) to remove his details from the database. 

* * *

**4.How gowealthy communicates through its members?**

  * Special Offers and Updates : We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on services and member benefits. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications by mailing us at [member@gowealthy.com](mailto:member@gowealthy.com). 
  * Service Announcements On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. Users may opt-out of these communications by mailing at [member@gowealthy.com](mailto:member@gowealthy.com).
  * Customer Service: We communicates with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes. 

* * *

**5.The users choices regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.**  
The website does not use personally identifiable information for reasons unrelated to the purpose for which the information was originally collected. The user opt-out of having his/her personally identifiable information used for unrelated purposes via email. The user opt-out of continued use by the website for unrelated purpose by contacting us via email or by an e-fax. 

* * *

**6\. The security measures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Gowealthy control.**

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide services to you or in order to do their jobs. 
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that protect personal information about you.
  * Your Gowealthy Account Information is password-protected. 
  * In certain areas Gowealthy uses industry-standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions.   
If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to [support@gowealthy.com](mailto:support@gowealthy.com)

* * *

**7\. How will the users be notified if Gowealthy change this privacy policy?**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. 

* * *

**8\. How user can correct any inaccuracies in the information?**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can usually be done at the member interface page or by emailing our Customer Support at [member@gowealthy.com](mailto:member@gowealthy.com). 

* * *

**9\. Compliance with Children's Online Privacy Protection Act COPPA**   
Gowealthy does not knowingly solicit information from children or knowingly market its services to children. 

* * *

**10\. Public Forums Disclaimer**  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. You should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages.  We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. Exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

* * *
